Come on out, first student!   Why are you laughing?   Isn't she beautiful? Next! Come on out, RORA!  Does anyone need tissue? Do you understand how scary it is now? [The Silence of IDOL: BABYMONSTER]
[Night has arrived after a hectic schedule] Now that we took a shower, I want to go to bed. Right? I'm so sleepy. I'm going to sleep now. I'm sleepy. Isn't this bed too small?
I don't think the seven of us can sleep here. I should sleep on the floor. I'll just sleep here.  Who can it be? - Who is this? - A ghost?   Here's your mattress. Can you give me some space?
Your Korean is very good-yo!  Okay. I'll get going then. Wait. Are you just leaving it here? It's super easy so install it yourselves. Okay. - Okay. Bye. - Thank you.
We're just like the kids at a retreat.  Hold the ends. Hold them.    It's like gimbap. Let's go. Oh, cool!  I did it!    But since it (the mattress) is wrapped airtight,
all we needed to do was take it out. - Exactly. - How convenient. It just takes one person to do it.  Take a seat. I love it. We can sleep here. Here...   What is it? A candy? What is it?
Who wants to have a candy? Me? We'll play a game to make it fair. A game?  [Push your competitor out of the bed while sitting down!]   Here we go!  This is... I'm not up.  Push her out! Come here.
Just quit.  RAMI is the winner! Congratulations. My candy. That was super fun.   Just what are you doing now? What are you doing? Aren't you the delivery guy? We've met, no? He has two jobs.   RAMI!
RAMI! What do you have in your hand? Nothing. I saw something yellow. That's yellow. Oh, my hair? Mine's yellow, too.  Not that. Give me that! What happens if you eat a candy before you go to bed?
It's yummy! It is yummy. Your teeth will rot. No.  I'm confiscating it. He's confiscating it! I had this a lot when I was a baby. Make sure you clean up your bed first and go to sleep.  When I see you
practicing for the talent show, I'll take that as you don't want to sleep, so I'll make sure you fall asleep forever. Everyone, go to sleep!  This pillow is so comfy and cool. Right?
I felt a bit hot while playing the game, but I can feel myself cooling down. This is great for hot weather. It was so comfy that I dozed off for a bit. I did, too. It's so comfy.
I want to take this home.  Hang on a second. Wake up! Wake up!  Tomorrow is the talent show. We shouldn't let the seniors students beat us. No way. Let's go all the way.
Let's practice hard and go to sleep. I'll turn it on. Let me press 'play'.     (Avoiding the instructor) Should we turn off the music?  Let's be professional.     What's going on?
Are you sure you're asleep? This won't do.  It's cold. - Are you cold? - Yes.  Are you comfortable like that? What's going on? I guess you rolled out of your bed.   Everyone, close your eyes.
What are you doing still up? Everyone's asleep. Again.  It's me.  Come on. Where's my partner?   Go dance!     Do it properly! What are you doing still up?   What's with the door? Open it!
Get rid of this matress now! Okay. Who did this?  If there's any bed left... There's none.  This won't do. You're one team at this retreat. You are a team. Even if I catch just one of you,
you'll have to participate in a group mission as a whole. Everyone make a line! 1, 2, 3. Get up! If you succeed in the group mission, I'll get you an item so you can sleep better.
That is, if you succeed. But! If you fail, you'll be given a penalty item. Your group mission is to become a human fan. The seven of you will have to pose in the shape of a fan and stay that way.
Start now! I'll go fourth. - I'll go third. - I'm good as long as I'm not the first. That's the first. The one here must be strong. That's not me.  Who's the strongest? CHIQUITA. Lie down here.
Okay. Go! You should go down more. Everyone should depend on each other. Why is it so far? Okay. Come on. 1, 2, 3, 4. Go on! Make the fan shape.  Give me your hand. Get up! I'm sweating.
That was okay. Although it wasn't perfect, it was okay as the first mission. Thank you. Salute! Since you nailed the first mission, I'll give you an item to sleep well.
Come forward, CHIQUITA and RAMI. Yes, sir! - It's an eye mask. - How cute. Thank you. Wear it now. Give me a cute pose. I'm cute even if I'm not doing anything.  1, 2, 3. Good. That's it!
Go to bed now! I'll get going, then.   Good night.  - Shall we practice again? - Cool.  CHIQUITA, you're at the center.      RURU! Slay it! ]   BOUT IT BOUT IT I'm feeling the rhythm all over.
Everybody get down  My head is about to explode.  I can't take it anymore. Here comes your second group mission. Your group mission is called 'Cheek-to-cheek', You'll be paired with your eyes closed.
In 20 seconds, you have to guess what it is between your cheeks. What's the first item? - What's this? - Get closer. Good. A scrunchie? A sock? A slipper?  You've used half the time.
The time is almost up. Squishy. - A humidifier? - A doll?  5, 4, 3, 2, 1  Take it out. What do you think it is? Say it now.  RORA's sleeping socks? I don't give out my sleeping socks.
Is that why it smelled? It didn't smell! It wasn't a sock. - What is it? - You can get it right. A scrubber? You keep saying scrubber. The answer is... A shower ball. It is a scrubber.
There's no sock like this.  The next team should close their eyes, too.  Start now! You have to put your weight into it. She's adjusting to RUKA's height. What is it? There height isn't compatible.
What do you think it is? You've used half the time. Ten seconds have gone. Is this some type of a musical instrument? You're not that far off. Not far off? Last five seconds. 5, 4, 3 2 , 1
What do you think it is? What is it?  MATH  "Soroban"? She got it in Japanese. She got it in Japanese. In Japanese, it's called "soroban". I don't speak Japanese. Help me.
We call it "jupan" in Korean. Correct.  How did you know? Do you know what this is? - No. - I do. Do you know what it is? You use it to solve math problems. Let's start now!   It's not there yet.
It's soft, isn't it? Where are you going?  Where are you going? Think carefully. Ten seconds have passed. You have ten seconds. Isn't this the scrub? Isn't it a scrub? 5, 4
- I don't know! - 3, 2, 1. Done! I'll give you the chance to say the answer. SHEESH It used to be your part.    I'll give you three seconds. 1, 2, 3  You failed! You have to finish that sentence.
No. Time's up. Don't you know what it is? CHIQUITA doesn't know.  You used to say that a lot. Our 'jegi' dance. How disappointing. - That's the way you kick 'jegi'. - Really? Since RUKA got it right,
you'll choose two students who will get the penalty item.     Who else didn't do a good job? ASA. I did well. RORA and ASA. We're ROSA. RORA and ASA, come follow me. What? We're going to hell.
What? I'm scared. WELCOME TO HELL  You will not recognize your dear friends.  Come on out, first student!   It's an art piece. Why are you laughing?  Isn't she beautiful?  You look good. ASA-lisa.
Move your arms. Good. This is my favorite outfit.  Next student! Come on out, RORA!  Does anyone need tissue? Your outfit is comfortable, right? Right? Very flexible too.
Have you realized just how scary I can be?  Go back to bed quietly. Go to sleep! Go!  Good. Cover her with your tissue.  Good. You're sleeping well.  This is hilarious. Get up, tissue.
She looks like fried tofu from the back. Here it comes.    [With ASA-lisa & Tissue RORA BABYMONSTER dances under the moonlight] It must be so uncomfortable. Come at the back.       No way. RORA.
I'm tissue. Tissue?  Why are you here? Come out now! Look how other model students are sleeping soundly. Go back to sleep.    [BABYMONSTER decides to take a revenge on the instructor]
We have to take a revenge. When he comes back, shall we just stay still, not sleeping? We could admire Mona Lisa. Good. You can use the tissue if you get teary.   Prepare to admire Mona Lisa.
How beautiful.  But this is not the time to admire this beautiful piece of art. It's time for you to sleep. Lie down! Lie down? Lie down! In bed. Sleep in your beds! Tissue! Go lie down.
Shall I practice, taking this costume off? (Instructor is scary) Do it secretly.  Let's go!        Let's dance together. I'll make sure you sleep forever. What's going on? Everyone quiet!
I can't take this no more. I'll give you the hardest mission.  You must put the rings around my horns. I'll run around and you'll have to put the rings on my horns.
If you manage to put 20 rings within a minute, you're good.   No! Don't come near me! EASY PEASY~   No! You shouldn't hold my horns. 30 seconds have passed.  You can't put your head down suddenly.
Last ten seconds! No. Hold on! This isn't right. You kept touching the horns that they're broken. They are not!  Did we fail? Now, I'm going to give a very special penalty item to RUKA. Ta-da!
We have a new friend.  She's from somewhere very far. Come on out, RUKA.  So cute.  You'll sleep like this. It suits RUKA so well. Act like the alien is kidnapping you. Like this? I finally got RUKA!
No more practicing! Sleep with your alien friend till the morning comes. You should use the mattress by yourself.    RUKA, at least take your shoes off and go to sleep.  The instructor is laughing.
"They are sleeping well~"   It's okay. My alien friend hasn't eaten. He's gone. He's dead. Bring him back to life.         We were perfect. - Perfect. - That's right.
I guess the alien wants to take a rest.  He says it was tiring. Let's go to sleep.   Good night. Bye.  [Please look forward to the full version of BABYMONSTER sleeping]  Get up, everyone!
Everyone, up! Yes, sir. Did you sleep well with the Greenie? Greenie is sick. Greenie is sick. Why has he gone so flat? He's sick because of you. Get up! It's time for the talent show. Right!
Today is the talent show. Get up! We shouldn't let the senior students to walk all over us. Let's go slay the stage. Greenie should go to the ER. Greenie is dead. Bye.
Do you know there's a fan meeting in Seoul in August? - Whose? - BABYMONSTER. BABYMONSTER? I know! We're performing 'FOREVER' by BABYMONSTER tomorrow. Will we get to listen to them performing live?
Probably?